I know it was 11% at the start, but does that creep up during the trial?
Anything you can say?
I think, with respect to PCSK9s, I believe they've also been in line with what we saw
earlier in the study.
But we can follow up with the details.
I know the GLP-1 data for sure, but I don't recall that the PCSK9s are a source of concern
either.
Brilliant.
Thank you very much, Fash.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of Michael Leighton from Jefferies.
Please go ahead.
Thank you.
Question from Oracle.
So, just a quick follow-up, please.
The guidance for mid- to high-single-digit C or EBIT growth in the second half seems to
imply more cost control, especially taking into consideration the EVIT-T R&D phasing that
you just mentioned.
Can you talk about the P&L dynamics?
Like, where are you containing costs, and is that something that we need to take into
consideration as we think about 27?
Or is that sort of tucking in expenses that will not recur?
Thank you.
Thanks, Michael, for the question.
So, from a P&L dynamics perspective, two things I'd say is, H1 to H2, we always have, from
a profitability perspective, from a spend perspective, H2 being a higher spend half.
For example, Q2, our profitability finished with 41.2% operating margin, and we know
that Q2 is typically the most profitable quarter, so to say.
So that part of the dynamic will remain going into this year as well.
In terms of where we are working from a productivity perspective, things have been pretty consistent
from beginning of the year.
Beginning of the year, we said we'll continue our productivity measures when it comes to
our manufacturing operations.
Operations is done very well.
Gross margin would be pressured as the portfolio shifts, but productivity should help us keep
gross margins more or less to where second half.
Thank you.
This is a very interesting concept.
I think it's going to be a very interesting topic, and I'll add on to what we were saying
earlier about the profitability of the capital.
And the capital should be in the capital, and we should be able to keep it in the capital
as well.
So we'll keep it in the capital, and we'll keep it in the capital as well.
And then, I think, on R&D, we will continue to invest what the pipeline needs.
And this would mean incremental investments this year on the back of Avidity, but also
a couple of other assets that we took on, including Tourmaline, Regulus, and Anthos last
year.
And then, SG&A, the percentage of sales is a place where we believe we as a company can